All right, we're back in the car. I was
not going to make this video, but I've
realized I need to make this video
because I have been living the lesson
that I have to share with you. And I
think this is going to really help you
if you can grab on to this. When we're
building our businesses,
we have things that we have to do. And
life happens. Life comes up that causes
us to sometimes
go off track or get distracted or things
happen. Let me just give you a little
bit of what I've been dealing with. Last
week, we had to tear out a wall in our
house, an exterior wall.
Um, we had to get our roof replaced. And
then this week, Monday, the power went
out, so I had to go across town to do
some work. Tuesday, yesterday, the
internet went out all day. And then I
found out this morning, for some reason,
my Wi-Fi router is fried. So, even
though the internet's back up, if I plug
it in, my whole house has no internet.
So, I have to go get a Wi-Fi router. All
while I've been launching two campaigns
with clients, launching my own marketing
campaign and building that. And I have
coaching calls that I've had to do. I
have coaching clients that I have to
talk with. I'm creating content like
this. While everything the last 2 weeks
has been going not so optimally how I
would want them to go on a daily basis.
Nobody wants to have their roof rifted
off or their h exterior house or their
internet or their power go out. But
those are life things that happen,
right? Except I just had them all happen
within a week. So that's kind of crazy.
But here's what I want to talk about is
how to stay on track and not let those
things derail you when things don't go
how you want them to. You know, for
instance, I mean, here's another thing.
Let's say that you run a marketing
campaign, you invest $10,000 into a
campaign and it does not produce the
result that you want. Well, that would
be tragic, of course. But the sooner
that you can get resilient and get back
up again and keep going and you don't
let what's going on around you, what's
happening in your life to derail you,
the more you are able to reach your
goals. This creates a level of
resilience
and consistence to where you stay
consistent with the actions that you're
doing. Think about it like you as if
you're brushing your teeth. Think about
it as if you take a shower, right? And
and listen, I know some some of y'all
don't take a shower more than once a
week. That's that that's your
prerogative. But what I what I want to
say is those are habits that you do
regardless of what's going on in your
life. We had a situation a couple years
ago where the the water wasn't good
enough to even shower in our house. We
had to go out of our house to shower
every couple of days uh at a local gym
that was providing it to our area
because the water was uh toxified or
something like that. It happened. Yeah,
weird stuff happens when you live in the
city in Texas in Austin, Texas. Uh but
all that to say, it used to throw me so
off track from my creativity, from my
ability to show up for my family, from
my ability to show up for my clients.
And I remember in the past I would lose
deals. I would lose out on what I was
trying to accomplish. I would miss out
on the things that I had intended to do
because of all the stuff that was going
on in my life. And here's what I found
is that if you can learn the skill and
the art of staying present, of not
letting what's going on around you
affect you, of staying focused on what
you need to do, and then learning.
Listen, of course, I get frustrated,
disappointed. I spent two hours this
morning wrestling with my Wi-Fi router.
That like felt like so much wasted time,
right? Not happy about it. But then I
got over it. And I got over it quickly.
And I got over it as fast as I felt it.
Of course, I feel pain, disappointment,
frustration,
uh, anger when stuff happens, but if
I've learned anything, having two kids,
going through, we had this crazy
insurance claim with a hail stom happen
and just life and building business and
then seeing what happens when
entrepreneurs that are
multi-millionaires build business. I
remember seeing my mom, she's a
multi-millionaire entrepreneur.
mom, one of my number one mentors in my
life. And I remember seeing her go
through health challenges and literally
like be in the hospital and yet still be
able to stay focused with sending a text
to her team members as far as what to do
to keep the business running and making
millions of dollars and yet still also
resting when she needs to. Not this
hustle and grind of, well, I got to make
it work, right? This stress, this anger.
No, no, no, no. I'm talking about a
burnoutfree,
stressfree approach where you learn to
go with the flow even when things are
not going how you want them to.
And you learn to accept the stuff that's
not going how you want it to. And you
learn to even become, dare I say, okay
with it when things are not going how
you want them to. And and so I just saw
a license plate across me. It says,
"Daddy's money, but I'm daddy." I'm
like, "That's great. I need that. I love
that." Um, but anyways, when stuff
doesn't go how you want it to, learning
to not just like be numb to it, but to
say, "Okay, this is great. This is a a a
thing that can help us. We're improving
things in our life." You find the bright
side to it. You always find the bright
side to every situation. Like even if
you lose money in a marketing campaign,
what did you learn from that? Learning
to be resilient from those things when
they happen. Learning how to get back up
again, get back on the horse, keep
grinding forward, keep moving forward,
and do so in a state of peace and ease
and enjoyment and fun and happiness.
This is I've learned this having two
kids because you got to keep your
spirits up or they will suffer. And and
it's not even like a fake keep my
spirits up. Like I got to like genuinely
find something inside of me to say happy
and excited and joyful. And I've found
like in the past I used to disassociate
and it was like a fake it till you make
it type of a thing. Now it's like I
fully accept okay this has happened. and
I got to go out and do this. I got to
deal with this. Stuff is not going how I
want it to. Let's get back up again.
Let's learn what did we learn from this?
How can we improve in the future?
And developing that resilience through
the frustration. You can feel the
frustration
and then let it go. And you learn how to
quickly move past what po you, what
pisses you off, what makes you feel
angry, frustrated, disappointed, upset.
quickly. You get over it quickly. You
don't let it fester in your mind. That's
the that's that's the real game right
there. Because we could say that we got
over it exteriorly, but then inside our
head, we're like still processing it and
it's bothering us still.
And I say this as somebody who like
suffered from this, really suffered from
it
for a long time where I would lose my
ability to be creative. I would lose my
ability to show up for my family and my
business.
And
it wasn't until I like I was like, you
know what, like just let go of trying to
control everything. Learn to let go of
trying to control all the stuff that's
outside of your control and control what
you can control.
And when you can learn to do that, you
will be unusually successful because
you're going to show up at a level that
most people don't show up at. You're
going to be able to like I actually got
excited that I had to go to the store to
go now go get a Wi-Fi router because I
was like I can record my YouTube video
while I'm on the way there. Like I got
excited to share this with you and I and
I literally knew what I wanted to talk
about.
And this
is a strategy that listen I I've gone
back to this constantly in my career.
But
I also know what it's like living on the
other side of it. Trying to build a
business on the other side of it. Trying
to build a business through striving and
stress and when things aren't going how
we want it to. And just feeling like
gosh, why is nothing working out? and
just wishing
that things were different.
And I can tell you on the other side of
that
you can develop the ability to be
resilient, to not let these things throw
you off, to not let them throw you off
track. you can develop the skill to be
able to
approach everything that you're doing in
your business objectively and say,
"Okay, like this happened. This is going
on.
What can I learn from it? And how can I
realign my nervous system? How can I
realign my joy and my happiness? And
then how can I tap into that creative
place in the midst of the hardest moment
that I'm dealing with right now at this
moment. Right? We have different levels
of hard that we deal with. But if you
can learn to where your heart does not
affect you the way that it always has
and that you can learn to find that
peace and that ease and that enjoyment
in the midst of the challenges, you will
be more successful
than your peers, than you've ever been,
than yourself. Really, it's just you
versus you. Think about that. just you
versus you alone, you're going to be
able to be more successful than overall
because of that resilience that you're
able to develop in yourself to do and
accomplish these things that maybe you
never thought were possible that maybe
felt like seems like this goes against
my personality. This goes against
everything that I know to be right.
Okay? Like like if you get passionate
about because I know people they're like
I can't do it right. I can't do it. That
used to be me and I can tell you on the
other side of it,
you can do it and you can accomplish
great things. You can do greater than
you ever imagined
and you can experience the life and the
business that you want. My friends,
listen. And if you are a coach or a
mentor and you want to grow in your
business, I'd love to see you in my
Wealthy Coach Academy program. You can
check out the link below to see how to
get started with that. How we're helping
our clients grow and make tens of
thousands of dollars, even up to
hundreds of thousands of dollars per
month in their businesses by jumping
into our Wealthy Coach Academy program
today. I'll see you in there. Share this
video with somebody. Subscribe. We'll
talk soon. Have a good one.